没上过解剖课可不行 不过没事
Could've done without the anatomy lesson, but that's okay.
我会在治疗的时候解决的
I'll work that shit out in therapy.
贝丝…
Well, Beth...
这就是你大半夜偷偷溜进一个男人的卧室
That's a risk you take when you sneak into a man's bedroom
会遇到的风险
in the middle of the night.
那倒是
Don't I know it.
还有酒!
And a drink. Oof!
看来这消息要么特别好 要么差得不得了
This news must be real good or real bad.
我活了37年
In my 37 years,
只独自在这过夜过一次
I've only spent the night here alone once.
你知道的 房子里满是人的时候
You know, houses, they don't make noises
不会发出声音 但是空荡荡时…
when they're full of people but when they're empty...
天啊 会有呻吟声 吱吱声 还会不断移动
Man, they moan and they creak and they shift in place.
我觉得房子会与地基撕裂
I thought the house was going to tear itself out
然后跑路
from the foundation and walk away.
所以 我想我就在这过夜好了
So, I figured that I would just spend the night
确保它不会把你带走
and make sure it doesn't walk away with you.
我不…
I don't uh...
我不介意房子空荡荡着
I don't mind an empty house.  Mm.
骗子
Liar.
我…
I'll, uh...
我去帮你准备一下房间
I'll get your room ready.
噢 我的房间已经准备好了 爸爸
Oh, my room's ready enough, Dad.
你准备睡觉了嘛？
You ready to turn in?
开玩笑呢?
You kidding?
我五分钟就能睡着
I'm five away from sleep.
听着 我可以下楼去的
Look, I can go downstairs.
不 不用 亲爱的 你……
No, no, honey. No, you're...
你在那就很好
You're fine right there.
你在看什么?
What are you reading?
《旷野的慰藉》
The Solace of Open Spaces.
强硬就是脆弱
"To be tough is to be fragile.
温柔才是真正的凶狠
To be tender is to be truly fierce."
真正的慰藉无处可寻
"True solace is finding none.
也就是说 它无处不在
Which is to say, it's everywhere.
是啊 我不太相信
Yeah. Not sure I believe that.
是真的 贝丝 无处可寻
It's true, Beth. Can't be found.
上帝知道我找过了
Lord knows I've looked.
不对…慰藉…想发现得
No... Solace... must be discovered.
怎么发现?
Discovered how?
我需要个例子 因为…
I need an example, 'cause, um...
嗯 我也到处找遍了
Well, I've looked everywhere, too.
我整晚都在门廊盯着群山
I spent all evening on the porch staring at mountains,
听着鸟叫...
listening to birds...
但我的心空荡荡的
Heart still empty.
我想像洗泥土一样把它洗去
I take a shower to wash it away like dirt
但是 寂寞是洗不去的
but you can't wash lonely off.
所以 我与之共存了
So, I surrender to it.
我所能做的就是孤独地睡去
Best I can do is sleep through the lonely,
前提是我能睡着的话
if I can sleep at all.
结果 我走进来 发现你在这
Then I walk in here and I discover you.
现在我的内心满满当当
Now my heart's full.
我真希望你能活得比我久 贝丝
I sure hope you outlive me, Beth.
我不确定我是否能容忍这个没有你的世界
I'm not sure I could tolerate the world without you in it.
别担心 爸爸
Worry not, Daddy.
只有好人死得早
Only the good die young.
如果今晚有流星撞击地球
If a meteor strikes earth tonight,
明天就会只剩下我和蟑螂
it is me and the cockroaches
管理这地方了
running this motherfucker tomorrow.
那看来明天是我的幸运日
Well, I guess tomorrow's my lucky day, then.
晚安 宝贝女儿
Good night, baby girl.
晚安 爸爸
Good night, Daddy.
翻译：业余渣翻人
谢谢你
Thank you.
他需要这
He needed this.
我们都需要
We both do.
我们找个房子租下来吧
Find us a house to rent.
这段时间还是不和父亲们住了
We're done living with fathers for a little while.
我已经感觉好多了
I feel better already.
我的心灵
In my soul.
这才是最重要的
That's all that matters.
他没事吧?
Is he okay?
嗯…
Well...
他只是个被迫做了男人该做的事的男孩
He's a boy who was forced to do what men do.
这些日子 大多数男人都不愿意去做了
These days, most men won't even do it.
因为社会教导他们作为一只羊
because society has taught them that they are sheep.
狼来的时候 不要反抗
And when wolves come you must not fight them.
要去找牧羊人帮忙
You must call a shepherd.
所以 他在对本应该得到表扬的事情
So, he feels guilt for doing something
感到内疚
he should be praised for.
再出几次汗 莫会带他上山
A few more sweats, then Mo will take him up on the hill.
下山后
Then when he comes down,
他就不会觉得自己是杀人凶手了
he won't think of himself as a killer.
他会觉得自己是个战士
He'll think of himself as a warrior.
跟你一样
Like you.
我都算不上是战士
I'm hardly a warrior.
你有多内疚?
How much guilt do you feel?
我唯一的遗憾是 不是我亲手把他杀了
My only regret is that I didn't kill him myself.
这就是战士会有的遗憾
That's a warrior's regret.
今天你就把那马给米娅 劳埃德
Give that horse to Mia today, Lloyd.
你骑母马栏里的棕色新马
Pull that new bay from the mare corral.
那母马得骑一下
She needs ridin'.
这是我的坐骑 我他妈才不去骑母马呢
This is my mount. I ain't riding a fucking mare.
那你就滚蛋
Then you'll walk.
带着那男孩 教他怎么套马鞍
And take that boy and show him how to saddle a horse.
来吧 孩子
C'mon, kid.
记住我说的话
Memorize what I say:
角 鞍桥 裙 座 索具…
Horn, pommel, skirt, seat, rigging...
重复一遍
Repeat it.
角、鞍桥
Horn, pommel,
裙 座 索具
skirt, seat, rigging.
肚带 皮带
Cinch, latigo,
马蹬…
stirrup...
D型环
D rings.
背带
Back billet.
肚带 皮带 马蹬
Cinch, latigo, stirrup,
D型环 背带
D rings, back billet.
不错
Good.
把它系上吧
Let's toss it on her.
好 往上套
Okay, go.
好了 从她下面把肚带抓住
Okay, reach under her and grab that cinch.
肚带
Cinch.
好 皮带穿过D型环
Okay, latigo goes through your Dring.
往上回穿
Back up and through.
再次穿过D型环
Back through that Dring again.
拉紧
Pull it up snug.
很好 后肚带也一样
Good, now the same thing on the back cinch.
行了
All right.
现在你是这皮带的持有者
Now this is your latigo keeper.
上面刻有制鞍师的名字
It's got the name of the saddlemaker right on it.
你会识字吗?
Can you read?
会
Yeah.
好的 我骑的是斯特林的
Okay. I ride a Sterling.
达顿先生 他骑的是戴尔·哈伍德或者唐·里奇的
Mister Dutton, he rides a Dale Harwood or a Don Rich.
里普骑的是安迪·马施克的
And Rip, he rides an Andy Maschke.
其他人骑什么?
What do the others ride?
不重要 他们自己给马备鞍
Don't matter. They saddle their own horses.
劳埃德 等你搞定了
Lloyd, when you're done with that,
把面板移到竞技场里
start moving them panels into the arena.
什么事 先生?
Yes, sir?
帮我接通立监狱典狱长电话
Can you get the state prison warden
好吗?
on the line for me, please?
当然
Of course.
先生 杰弗里斯典狱长在一号线
Sir, Warden Jeffries is on line one.
过得怎么样 先生?
How are you, sir?
他有公设辩护律师或法律顾问吗?
Does he have a public defender or counsel?
谢谢你！
Thank you.
首席检察官达顿 找理查德·斯科特
Attorney General Dutton for Richard Scott.
斯科特先生 我要访问一下你的客户特雷尔·里金斯
Mr. Scott, I need to interview your client Terrell Riggins
关于他参与
in regards to his involvement
约翰·达顿谋杀未遂案
in the John Dutton attempted murder.
没那必要
That won't be necessary.
因为我要给他豁免权
Because I'm offering him immunity.
妈的!
Shit!
那他妈是什么?
What the fuck is that?
蜈蚣
That's a centipede.
咬到你了吗?
It get you?
啊 是的 咬到了
Uh, yeah. It got me.
大多数人在德州都不会睡地板上的
Most people in Texas don't sleep on the ground.
我给你带了点早餐
I brought you some breakfast.
有叉子吗?
You got a fork?
当作吃三明治好吗
Make a sandwich out of it.
你是谁?
Who are you?
我是吉米 我是新来的牛仔
I'm Jimmy. I'm the new cowboy.
你才不是牛仔
You're not a cowboy.
为什么这么说?
What makes you say that?
我能从你的眼中看出来
I can see it in your eyes.
你是人家安排来这里的
You're somebody somebody told to come here
这样我们就能把你训练成牛仔了
so we can make a cowboy out of you.
差不多吧
Something like that.
这是别人所看不到的
It's the most glorious work you can do
最高荣誉的工作
that nobody ever sees.
占据你的每一寸肌肤
Takes every inch of you.
你得冒着自己与马的生命危险
You're gonna risk your life and your horse's life.
没人会知道你赢了还是输了
And nobody's knows if you won or if you lost.
这是一直到你死去的那一天都没有观众的艺术
It's art without an audience 'til the day you die.
即使是你死后
And then after you're dead,
也没有观众
you don't have an audience either.
你只是消失了
You're just...you're just gone.
现在 你必须让自己想要这样的生活
Now, you gotta want this life.
你必须从骨子里去接受它
You've got to want it all the way to your bones.
不然的话..
And if you don't...
绝对会是人间地狱的
it can be absolute hell on earth.
我不知道我想要什么
I don't know what I want.
我们这些老家伙在这
There's a few of us old goats hanging around.
会确保你不会挨饿
We'll make sure you don't starve.
还有 别再睡在地上了
Oh, and quit sleeping on the ground.
找个长凳什么的
Find yourself a bench or something.
不然你会发现自己依偎在一条响尾蛇旁边
Otherwise you'll find yourself cozied up next to a rattlesnake.
长凳 知道了
Bench. Got it.
有什么好玩的吗？
Got me something saddled?
我们只是去找些新马
We're just going to gather twoyear olds.
半小时后回来
Hell, we'll be back in a half an hour.
那时候才好玩
That's when all the fun starts.
好吧 我才不想驯那些马 它们会乱叫
Well, I ain't breaking no colts, for crying out loud.
我今天的乐趣就这了
This is the only fun I get today.
小子 让我们看看你学到了什么
Boy, let's see what you've learnt.
为达顿先生备马鞍
Saddle Blaze for Mister Dutton.
已经装上马鞍了
It's already saddled.
行 把它带过来
Well, go on and get him.
还叫"小子"啊?
Still "boy", huh?
是啊 他可呆不到取名字那天 先生
Yeah, he ain't gonna be around long enough to name, sir.
是啊 如果他铲屎那么糟糕的话
Yeah, well, if he's that bad at shoveling shit,
我绝对不会想让他给我的马备鞍的
I damn sure don't want him saddling my horse.
他铲屎倒是挺好的
He can shovel shit with the best of them,
不过他把你的女儿惹毛了
but he got on the wrong side of your daughter, though.
嗯
Hmm.
好了 检查一下肚带
All right.  Check your cinch.
帅气的小混蛋 是吧?
Handsome little sucker, aren't you?
我打赌这就是你所有麻烦背后的原因
I bet that's the cause behind every problem you got.
如果我是你 我会想办法变丑
If I was you I'd find a way to get ugly.
变丑？当然啰
Ugly?  And how.
为什么要变丑吗?
Why ugly?
帅气是我唯一的优势
Handsome's the only thing I got going for me.
这就是为什么
That's why.
你能再派些警员到
Can you send some more deputies
利文斯顿外地办事处吗?
to the field office in Livingston?
某种抗议
Some sort of protest.
所有人后退
Everybody back up.
你们不能堵住政府大楼的入口
You cannot block the entrance to a government building.
你就是该死的畜生！
You're the fucking animal!
所有人给我蹲下!
Everybody down!
蹲下！
On the ground! On the ground!
快蹲下！
我受够了 让他们蹲着！
I'm sick of this shit. Keep them on the ground.
别对任何人开枪
Don't shoot anybody.
嘿! 把石头放下!
Hey!  Put the rocks down!
想都别想
Don't even think about it.
凯西 搞什么?
Kayce, what the fucking fuck?
你说呢
You tell me.
她们跑来这洒血在自己身上
They just showed up pouring blood on themselves
扔石头
and throwing rocks and shit.
我都不知道他们想要干什么
I don't even know what the fuck they want.
这就是他们想要的
This is what they want,
他们想在这作秀 凯西
they want the fucking shit show, Kayce.
而你却让他们如愿以偿了
And you just gave it to them.
操 亨顿 把枪放进枪套里
Fuck. Hendon, put the goddamn gun in your holster.
这是哈斯克尔
This is Haskell.
好了 开始吧
All right, here we go.
杰克 你驯红褐色秃脸
Jake. You're sorrel bald face
四肢袜脚的那匹
filly with four stocking feet.
伊森 贝柯尔特 布莱兹 先生
Ethan, bay colt, Blaze.  Sir.
瑞安 科尔比 你们驯鹿皮母马仔和棕灰公马仔
Ryan, Colby, you'll be Buckskin filly and dun Colt.
沃克 你驯闪光红罗纳马
And Walker, you're red rhone. blaze face.
发生什么事了？
Something happen?
我在处理
I'm working it out.
是啊 我看出来了 整个牧场的人也看出来了
Yeah, I see that. So can the whole ranch.
他们是得看看 先生
Well, they need to see it, sir.
我才不想听到 从你手里失手的
I don't want to hear about the wildfire that got away from you.
只想听成功的
Just the one you put out.
好的 先生
Yes sir.
无论他做了什么 别忘了他对你的意义
Whatever he did, don't forget who he is to you.
对我们俩的意义
To both of us.
正是由于他对我们的意义 先生
Who he is to us, sir,
他现在还能走路
is the reason why he's still walking.
怎么了
Yeah.
有什么?
There's what?
哦 天哪
Oh, jeez.
好吧 我马上就来
All right. I'm on my way.
瑞安
Ryan.
我们去为政府工作吧
Let's go work for the state.
发生了什么事?
What happened?
我都不知道该怎么解释
I don't even know how to explain it.
孩子 我估计我花一周的时间去想着怎么把
Son, if I spent a week thinking of ways
自己的一天搞砸 我都不会想到这个
to fuck up my day, I could not have come up with this.
医疗急救在哪儿?
Where's EMS?
那不是血
It ain't blood.
我想是油漆
It's paint, I think.
他们 呃 倒在自己身上
They, uh, poured it on themselves.
倒在自己身上? 是的
Poured it on themselves?  Yep.
你以前见过这样的事情吗?
You ever seen anything like this before?
自从我的单身派对之后就没有了
Not since my bachelor party.
你们为什么要这么做?
Why would you do that?
瑞安 瑞安 别跟她们说话
Ryan, Ryan, don't talk to them.
这都是照规定办事吗?
Was this all by the book?
当然 凯西被人群骚扰围攻
100%, Kayce was assaulted and rushed by the crowd,
他使用正当的武力制服了袭击者
he used justified force to subdue his assailant.
亨顿协助了他
Hendon came to his aide,
在我们到这之前 他们控制了人群
they controlled the crowd until we got here.
你有视频证明吗?
You got video to back that up?
哦 根本不缺视频 约翰
Oh, there's no shortage of video, John.
我敢肯定我们说话的时候全世界都在看着
I'm sure the whole world's watching this shit as we speak.
谁是这个马戏团的头头?
Who's the ring leader of this circus?
左边那个 金发
One on the left, blonde hair.
她在休斯顿 伯克利被捕
She's been arrested in Berkeley, Houston,
还有在波特兰 圣路易斯…
Portland, St. Louis...
扰乱和平 未能驱散
Disturbing the peace, failure to disperse.
让人解雇
All dismissed.
她叫什么名字?
What's her name?
萨默 希金斯
Summer Higgins.
你是萨默?
You Summer?
你一定是幕后大头目
You must be the big boss.
我只是个退休的大老板
I'm the retired big boss.
你可以看到我现在的结果
You can see how that's working out for me.
如果她们想的话 我可以给她们拿毯子盖住
I can get them blankets to cover up if they'd like.
我们的身体就是抗议
Our bodies are our protest.
她们才不想掩盖起来 但我知道这让你很困扰
They don't want to cover up, though I can see it bothers you.
男人把我们的乳房物化
Men objectify our breasts,
然后给全世界洗脑 让人们想着
and then brainwash the world into thinking
乳房应该被隐藏起来 只因为你们嫉妒
that they should be hidden to make up for your jealousy
或是对性冲动把持不住
or lack of impulse control,
这很讽刺 因为它们并不是为你们而创造
which is ironic because nature didn't make them for you.
大自然创造它们是为了喂养孩子
Nature made them to feed children,
不是你那些毒瘤的男性幻想
not your toxic male fantasies.
我明白了
I see.
但这不是我们来这里的原因
But that's not why we're here.
可不是嘛
You don't say.
我们在抗议
We're protesting the existence
国家支持保护工业畜牧业
of a statesponsored police force
警察部队的存在
that protects industrialized animal farming
以及每年对数以百万计的动物的屠杀
and the mass murder of millions of animals every year.
你耕过地吗 萨默?
You ever plow a field, Summer?
为了种植藜麦或高粱
To plant the quinoa or sorghum
或者你所吃的任何东西?
or whatever the hell it is you eat?
把地上甚至地下的一切都抹杀了
You kill everything on the ground and under it:
你杀了每条蛇 每只青蛙
you kill every snake, every frog,
每只老鼠、鼹鼠、田鼠、蠕虫、鹌鹑……
every mouse, mole, vole, worm, quail...
你把它们都杀了
You kill them all.
所以我想唯一真正的问题是
So, I guess the only real question is:
一种动物得有多可爱
how cute does an animal have to be
你才会去关心它是否是为了养活你才死?
before you care if it dies to feed you?
这些人大老远跑到这里来干什么?
What the hell are these people doing all the way out here?
地方那么多 看起来绝非偶然 是吧
Of all the places, doesn't seem too random, does it.
你想怎么办 凯西?
What do you want to do, Kayce?
起诉吧
Press charges.
这就是他们想要的 约翰
That's what they want, John.
我是说 他们想在新闻上看到这个
I mean, they want to see this on the goddamn news.
已经上新闻了
It's already on the news.
让他们在公众视野下五年
Let them stare five years in the face
看看他们还想策划多少抗议活动
and see how many more protests they want to plan.
行 好的
Okay, all right.
警官 把她扶起来
Officer. Let's get her up.
你因严重殴打一个平和的警察
You're under arrest for aggravated battery
被逮捕了
of a peace officer.
你有权保持沉默
You have the right to remain silent.
走吧
Let's go.
你所说的一切都将在法庭上
Anything you say can and will be used against you
作为呈堂证供
in a court of law.
如果你没有律师 会为你指派一名
If you don't have a lawyer, one will be appointed to you.
我孤单却快乐
I'm lonesome but happy
富有过 却破产了
Rich, but I'm broke
上帝知道原因
And the good Lord knows the reason
我只是个牛仔
I'm just a cowpoke
从夏安到道格拉斯
From Cheyenne to Douglas
都是我所知道的范围
The ranges I know
因为我随风飘荡
Cause I drift with the wind
没有人在乎我去哪
Noone cares where I go
劳埃德在那边跃跃欲试的样子
Lloyd's chomping at the bit over there.
我一分都没有
I ain't got a dime
穿着破旧的牛仔裤
In these old wornout jeans
于是我不吃牛排了
So I'll stop eating steak
还是吃回豆子吧
I'll go back to beans
她很聪明
She's sensible.
最好后面有繁殖计划
Better breeding program, lately.
妈的 我想这只好了 老大
Hell, I think this one's done, boss.
下一匹
Let's get another.
干得不错
Nicely done.
把它拿下 伊森!
Get him, Ethan! Yeehee!
好的 先生! 不错 伊森
Yes, sir! All right, Ethan.
很高兴你没有被甩下马
Glad you didn't get bucked off.
不然我们会让迪特上马的
We'd have had Teeter get on there.
这匹马不错 老大
Pretty nice horse there, boss.
对它来说 第一天不错了
That's a pretty good first day for him.
啤酒时间到了
It's beer time.
啤酒时间到
Beer o'clock.
最后三匹你驯
The last three are yours.
就这?
After all I've done for you?
劳埃德 你表现得像个老大
Lloyd, you start acting like a boss,
那我就对待你像老大一样
and I'll fucking treat you like one.
所以 我现在是下等人了
So I'm low man now
就因为做了你也会做的事情
for doing something you would've done.
正是因为你为我所做的
It's only because of what you've done for me
你才没有在那边
that you ain't over there shoveling shit
和那臭小子一起铲屎
with that fucking boy.
你还有剩马可以驯 很幸运了
You're lucky you have any horses to break at all.
那狗东西本该死了
That son of a bitch should be dead.
妈的 劳埃德 但他没死
Goddamn it, Lloyd, but he ain't.
达顿先生想让他在这 所以你猜怎么着?
Mister Dutton wants him here, so guess what?
那他就可以呆在这里
He's fucking here.
没人比我更想让那
There ain't nobody that wants that son of a bitch dead
狗东西去死
more than me,
但是农场要摆到第一位
but the ranch comes first.
你忘了那一点
And you forgot that.
加油! 加油 谢德
Come on!  Come on, Shad.
他妈的快点 你要错过了!
Hurry it the fuck up, you're going to miss it!
那是你表亲戚?
That's your cousin?
是的 加油 宝贝 轻轻松松
Yep. Come on, baby. Clean run. Clean run.
给他们展示一下 流畅操作
Show them how to do it, smooth run.
流畅且轻松
Smooth run. Clean. I want it clean.
给我展示一次轻松的操作
Do a clean run for me this time.
这就是我们所需要的 只要拿下这个
It's all we need, just got to get this one.
看看他有多流畅 看 加油
Watch how smooth this is, watch this. Come on.
加油 加油
Come on, come on!  Woo, woo!
加油!
Come on!  Oh, yeah.
妈的 太快了!
God damn, that is fast!
就是那样! 那才是套索 ! 混蛋
That's how we do it!  That's roping, motherfucker!
就是那样！
That's how we do it.
嗯 该死 太棒了
Mmhmm.  Damn, that's good.
显然 套索的能力不会遗传
Clearly, the ability to rope is not hereditary.
什么? 去你妈的
What? Fuck you.
我比你强多了
I can outrope your fucking ass.
你他妈哪能比过我?
In what fucking world can you outrope me?
哪都行 别说地球了
In any world. Literally on any fucking planet.
我带你去外太空 然后把你比出去
I'll take you to outerspace and I'll outrope your fucking ass
外太空 我不在乎
in outerspace. I don't care.
你在外太空到底要用
What the hell kind of roping are you going to do
什么绳索?  地心引力
in outer space? It's called gravity.
你们他妈的都在说什么
What the fuck are you all talking about,
在太空套索?
roping in fucking space?
他说的! 太他妈疯狂了
He is!  That's fucking insane.
你和那男人有一样的基因 ?
You have the same DNA as that man?
你说得对 我不是一个人做的…
You're right, I didn't do it by myself...
你在说什么呢
What are you talking about
在干什么呢？
Whatcha doin'?
什么也没干
Nuthin'.
也没事干 就等着疲倦
Ain't nothin' to do. Just waitin' to be tired.
有什么事吗?
Something wrong?
没有
Nah.
休息吧 很快就清晨了
Get some rest. Morning comes early.
不知道为什么人人都称它为早晨
Don't know why everyone calls it morning.
不管怎么说 凌晨四点都是晚上
Four a.m. is night time any way you slice it.
是啊 就当你是对的
Yeah, suppose you're right.
晚安
Good night.
你在外面干什么 宝贝?
What are you doing out here, babe?
我只是有点厌倦睡在拖车里了
I'm just kind of tired of sleeping in that trailer.
趁天气好 想在星空下睡一觉
Want to sleep out here under the stars while the weather's good.
如果你不介意的话
If that's all right with you.
我不这么认为 不是吗?
I don't think so.  No?
不
No.
为什么不? 你宁愿睡在那个小盒子里?
Why no? You'd rather sleep in that little box?
我们可以待在外面
Oh, we can stay out here.
但你不可能睡的
But you're not gettin' any sleep.
鸡蛋煎两面吗 凯西?
Eggs over easy, Kayce?
是的 先生 谢谢
Yessir, thank you.
不客气
You're welcome.
好吧 看看这栋
Okay, look at this one.
在普赖尔 在波兹曼和这的中间
It's in Prior, it's halfway between here and Bozeman.
有四十英亩 房子很好
It's forty acres. The house is nice.
我可以在居留地教书 带泰特回到他朋友身边
I could teach at the rez, get Tate back with his friends.
嗨,爸爸
Hey, Dad.
嘿 伙伴 你感觉如何?
Hey, buddy. How you feeling?
饿了
Hungry.
在桑拿房里待四天就会这样
Four days in a sweat lodge will do that to you.
你说的没错 爷爷
Boy, you ain't lying, Grandpa.
房子看起来不错
House looks nice.
是啊 我也这么认为
Yeah, I think so too.
给你 凯西 好的
Here you go, Kayce.  All right.
好的
Okay.
不饿吗?
Not hungry?
我在间歇性禁食
I'm intermittent fasting.
什么意思?
What's that mean?
中午之前 只喝咖啡 抽烟
Uh, nothing but coffee and cigarettes 'til noon,
之后我他妈想吃什么就吃什么
and then I can eat what the fuck I want
到六点就开始喝酒
until I start drinking at six.
我倒是想见见给你这食谱的医生
I'd like to meet the doctor who came up with that diet.
我调整了一下 这样可以适应我的生活方式
I've adapted it a bit to suit my lifestyle.
你今天在忙什么?
What are you working on today?
我有些事情得做
I got a few irons cooking.
什么事情？
What irons?
我宁愿先斩后奏 爸爸
I'd rather ask for forgiveness than permission on these, Daddy.
你不介意的话
If you don't mind.
介意 什么事?
I do mind. What irons?
我要接受市场股权集团的工作
I'm taking the job at Market Equities.
那就接受呗 然后呢?
So take the job, then what?
告诉我 这对我们有什么帮助
Tell me how that helps us.
我把它搞崩了就能帮到我们了
It helps us when I run it into the fucking ground.
你今天要做什么?
What are you doing today?
违背良心的事
Battling my conscience.
嗯
Mmm.
我可以给你一些建议 爸爸
Well, I'd offer advice, Dad,
但我从没遇到过这种情况
but I've never been in that situation.
我要走了
I gotta go.
爱你 嗯
Love you.  Mmm.
要去毁掉一个人的生活了
Off to ruin a life.
好的 亲爱的
Okay, honey.
不管了！
Fuck it.
你被保释了
You made bail.
怎么回事？
How'd I do that?
你为什么要保释我?
Why'd you bail me out?
你相信你所做的是对的
You believe what you're doing is right.
我不同意 但我…
I disagree but I...
我尊重它
I respect it.
我还不了你钱
I can't pay you back.
不需要
Not asking you to.
那你肯定还有求于我
You're gonna ask me something though.
我想…我想带你去看看我的农场
I'd like to... I'd like to show you my ranch.
你以为带我去参观你的农场
You think a tour of your ranch
就会改变我的信仰吗
is gonna change what I believe?
不会 但这可能让你更好地了解我
No, but it might help you understand me better.
也许能让我更好地了解你
Might help me understand you, too.
你肯定也能理解
Surely you can appreciate that virtually every fiber
我浑身上下的细胞都在对我说
of my being is screaming at me to not get in the pickup
不要跟这50岁迷人的白人男性上车
with the charming, white male in his 50s,
因为我根本都不认识他
who I don't know from fucking Adam.
50岁 有魅力 哈
Charming and in my 50s, huh.
我已经开始 更喜欢你了
I'm starting to like you better already.
但我明白你的意思
But I see your point.
我太天真了
It's naive of me.
别再朝我儿子扔石头了 好吗?
Don't throw any more rocks at my son, okay?
你能保证你不会攻击我
Do I have your word you're not gonna attack me
然后把我杀了 丢在树林里吗?
and kill me and leave me in the middle of a forest?
如果那是我的计划的话
If my plan was doing all that
我还挺愿意打乱我的计划的
I'm probably willing to break my word.
我相信你
I'm going to trust you.
好
Good.
我也会相信你的
I'm gonna trust you, too.
上车吧
Get in.
完全豁免
Full immunity.
好吧 问吧
Okay, ask away.
特雷尔 你可以回答他的问题
Terrell, you can answer his questions
不用担心被起诉
without fear of prosecution.
不管我说什么?
No matter what I say?
不管你说什么 你是州证人
No matter what you say. You are a State's Witness.
在这里面呢?
What about in here?
告密者可没有豁免权
Ain't no immunity for a snitch.
你会被保护性监禁
You'll be put into protective custody.
表现好的话 我们可以送你去
With good behavior, we can move you to
中级戒备的监狱
a medium security facility that is significantly
比这里舒服多了
more comfortable than this place.
说吧
Fire away.
你认识这个人吗?
Do you know this man?
是不是是这个人收买你
Did this man hire you to facilitate
去谋杀达顿一家子？
the murder attempt on the Dutton family?
有事吗?
Can I help you?
这就好像开车穿越一个不同的世纪
It's like driving through a different century.
你有没有意识到全世界都在承受着多大的压力?
Are you even aware of the strain the rest of the world is under?
我知道这里的压力
I'm aware of the strain here.
作为一个人 我不知道
I don't know how much longer we'll last.
我们还能撑多久 你知道吗?
As a people, you know?
我认为这颗星球
I don't think the planet's going
忍不了我们多久了
to tolerate us much longer.
那是因为人们不再与之共存地生活
That's because people have stopped living with it,
而是开始依靠它生活
and started living on it.
但你是对的
But you're right.
总有一天 地球会像剥死皮一样清理掉我们
There will come a time when Earth sheds us like dead skin.
这都将会是我们自己的错
And it will be our own fault.
我很惊讶 你能从这里看到这些
I'm surprised you can see that from here.
你在任何地方都能看到它 萨默
You can see it from anywhere, Summer.
不可能错过的
It's impossible to miss.
能容纳300人吗?
Can you accommodate 300 people?
这是蒙大拿最大的牧场
It's the largest ranch in Montana.
我们丹麦都可以容纳
We can accommodate Denmark.
新娘白天在想
The bride is thinking that during the day
可不可以郊外骑马或坐会牧草车……
maybe offer trail rides or hay rides...
婚礼上坐牧草车?
Hay rides at a wedding?
怎么?  他们还要不要来咬苹果
What? They want to fucking bob for apples
和套袋赛跑呢 盖尔?
and have sack races too, Gayle?
他们是从纽约来的 贝丝
They're from New York, Beth.  Ah.
他们想要牧场体验
They want the ranch experience.
我只是把牧场给你
Well, I'm just offering the ranch.
如果他们想要牧场体验 价格会翻倍
If they want the ranch experience, price doubles.
没问题
Won't be a problem.
7月28日可以吗？
Can you lock that July 28th date?
给我押金 就归你了
You send me a deposit, it's all yours.
有事 挂了
Gonna lose you. Gotta go.
请问有什么需要帮助的吗？
May I help you?
打扰一下
Excuse me.
女士?
Ma'am?
打扰一下
Excuse me.
打扰一下!
Excuse me!
我去喊保卫
I called security.
没事的
That's fine.
请把门关上
Close the door, please.
你想要什么 贝丝?
What do you want, Beth?
那是我的位置
That's my seat.
你的位置? 嗯
Your seat?  Mmhmm.
没错 鲍比
That's right, Bobby.
你坐到我位置上了
You're sitting in my seat.
我开了七个小时的车 就为了告诉你这事
Man, I drove seven hours just to tell you that.
我不知道你在说什么
I have no idea what you're talking about.
我是市场股权集团蒙大拿分部
I am the new president of Market Equity's
新总裁
Montana division.
我负责所有新开发项目
I oversee all new development.
哦 他们付给你的薪水一定很高
Oh. That must be quite the salary they're paying you.
祝贺你
Congratulations.
没有薪水 鲍勃
No salary, Bob.
没优先认股权
No stock options.
没百分比收益
No percentage of profit.
不知道你能不能猜到
I wonder if you can guess
是什么诱使我接受这份
what would entice me to take a job
百年以来
doing exactly what my family
与我家人背道而驰的工作
have been fighting against for a century.
施瓦茨迈耶的收益份额
Their interest in Schwartz and Meyer.
是他们的控股权 鲍勃
Their controlling interest, Bob.
是啊 你下错注了
Yeah. You bet on the wrong horse.
你被炒了
You are fired.
你也是 爱管闲事的婊子
You're fired too, you nosy bitch.
这一切都要搬到蒙大拿去了
All this shit, it's moving to Montana.
公事不顺？
Hard day at the office?
是啊 可以这么说
Yeah, you could say that.
秘密就是这样
That's the problem with secrets.
不会永远都是秘密
They don't stay secret forever.
是啊 确实
No. They don't.
能告诉我你的秘密吗?
Care to tell me yours?
你先
You first.
你做到了
You did it.
你摆脱了他
You got away from him.
你得到了你应得的工作
You got the job you deserve.
你做了 你说你会做的事情
You did everything you said you would do.
轮到我遵守我的诺言了
Now, I keep my word.
这是你孩子
Meet your son.
想到 乔治先生还蛮享受的
Come to think Mr. George, enjoyed them.
他一直都是爱好者
He's been quite a bunk rider,
他和萨尔提主席一起
and, uh, he got to see a lot of bunk riding
看了很多场
with Salty Chief.
我从来都不知道那是什么
And I never knew what that was.
那些马很强壮
They were powerful horses
如果你在这么大个国家 从马身上下来
if you're off by yourself in the big country.
你不会想从他们身上下来的
You didn't want to get off of one of 'em.
是啊 下来就上不去了
No, no, you can't get back on.
他们很可能不带你 自己回谷仓去了
They're liable to go back to the barn without ya.
是的 乔治先生深知这个事实
Yeah. Mr. George appreciated the fact
那些马心中有怒
that they had a little fire in them.
是啊 我喜欢它们有怒气的样子
Yeah, well, I like them to have a little bit of fire,
但是 妈的 你也不想天天都看牛仔竞技吧
but doggone, you don't want to have a rodeo every day.
是啊
No.
他骑着那匹从工头那里
He rode that little paint blue horse
买来的蓝色的马
that he'd bought off of a foreman
来到这个牧场
that joined the ranch here
那匹绝对是匹截牛马
that was sure enough a little cutting horse.
嗯…
And, uh...
他训了那匹马很久
he worked her a lot.
你准备好了吗?
You ready?
准备什么?
Ready for what?
准备工作
Ready for work.
拿上你的包 伙计 我们走了
Grab your bag, ol' boy. Let's go.
希望你汲取了里面所谈论的一些知识
Hope you soaked up some of what you heard in there.
汲取什么？
Soaked up some of what?
德州有三个神
There's three gods in Texas:
全能神 巴斯特·韦尔奇 还有乔治·斯特雷特
the Almighty himself, Buster Welch, and George Strait.
里面就有其中一个
You just met one of them.
那不是乔治·斯特雷特
That's not George Strait.
我希望上帝赏了你根大鸡巴 吉米
I hope the Good Lord gave you a big dick, Jimmie,
因为他肯定在你脑袋做了手脚
'cause he sure shorted you on brains.
你会骑马吗?
Can you ride?
我会骑马
Yeah, I can ride.
很好 因为他们要让我们骑公马驹
Good, 'cause they're sending us on colts.
驯过吗？
Are they broke?
没怎么驯
Oh, not so much.
不过等我们到那就驯好了
But, they will be when we get there.
要骑多久?
How long a ride is it?
穿越两个牧场 每个一万英亩
Oh, through two pastures. Ten thousand acres each.
不过也就两个
Just two, though.
来吧 伙计 上马鞍吧
Come on, old boy, let's saddle up.
放轻松 放轻松
Easy, easy.
嘿 嘿 让他安静下来
Hey, hey.  Settle him down.
你准备好了吗?
You ready?
好吧 让我们把这些狗东西驯好起来
All right, let's run the rank out of these sons of bitches.
一天结束 我们飞行着 哭泣着
By the end of the night We'd be flying or crying
谈论我们走向
Talking 'bout the times
死亡所花费的时间
We've spent living towards dying
所以不要停止奔跑 孩子 但也不要天真
So don't stop running, boy But don't be naive
因为在一天结束
'Cause we'll be flying or crying
我们会飞翔 也会哭泣
By the end of the night
你想开枪就开枪
You wanna shoot, shoot.
这将是谋杀
It'll be murder,
不过也不是你第一次掩盖了
but it won't be the first one you covered up.
下一集"黄石"…
On the next "Yellowstone"...
无论好事在哪里发生
Wherever something good is trying to happen,
都会有邪恶的东西试图阻止它
something bad is trying to stop it.
我就是邪恶的东西
I'm something bad.
工棚里没有我们这样些弃儿的位置
No room for outcasts like us in the bunkhouse.
喔
Whoo.
一切到此为止 全部
This ends here, all of it.
我不能要求你这么做
Can't ask you to do that.
这是我的工作 我来就好
It's my job. I'll do it.
《黄石》前情回顾…
Previously on "Yellowstone"...
这是谁?
Who's this?
这就是雇来杀我们的人
That's the man hired to kill us.
谁雇的?
Hired by who?
你得问你哥哥要他的监狱记录
You need to ask your brother for his prison records.
如果他找理由推脱 我们就有答案了
If he resists in any way, then we have our answer.
我的天
Oh, my God.
施瓦茨迈耶 管着黄石的北边
Schwartz & Meyer runs half the land
一半的土地
on the north side of the Yellowstone.
你是个公司掠夺者
You're a corporate raider.
来给股权市场工作吧
Come and raid for Market Equities.
你现在有施瓦茨迈耶的控股权
You have controlling interest of Schwartz & Meyer now.
你想要施瓦茨迈耶的股份
You want a piece of Schwartz & Meyer.
我要你的份额
I want your piece.
把份额给我 我人归你
You give me that, I'm yours.
起来跳舞啊 老头
Get up and dance, old man.
停下来!
Stop it!
要想打架 规矩是什么 劳埃德?
What's the rule about fighting, Lloyd?
是你他妈逼我这么做的
God damn you for making me do this.
他一直呆这 也好不起来
He's never gonna get better staying here.
在我们找到折中方案之前
I was thinking we can go up and stay at your father's place
我在想要不要去你父亲家那边住段时间
for a while until we can find another place close to here.
为什么我的孩子们都要离开 去寻求幸福呢
Why do all my children have to leave to find happiness?